Guide to the Leon F. Litwack Collection of Berkeley, California, Protest Literature
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Files, Series I; 4; (4 boxes)
  - File 11 (Box 2, Folder 26-27)
    - Campus Friends of STDW (org). STOP THE DRAFT WEEK AND POLITICAL POWER. (very light tan stock).
    - Campus Friends of Stop the Draft Week (org). TUES. MORNING 4AM. Docketed: 22 Apr 68.
    - Campus Friends of Stop the Draft Week (STDW) (org). SUPPORT STOP THE DRAFT WEEK / Tuesday April 16. Illustrated. Docketed: 15 April 66.
    - Campus Friends of War Resisters League (org). ANNOUNCING 2nd MEETING. Offwhite stock, illustrated.. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 28 Nov 67.
    - Campus Mobilization Committee (org). ANTI-WAR MOVEMENT / Where From Here? Illustrated. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout noon Wed 26 April 67.
    - Campus Movement for a New America (org). PRESENTS PAUL KRASSNER. Variant flyer. Docketed: Ban-Tel handout noon Mon, 1 May 67.
    - Campus Peace and Freedom Party (org). PEACE & FREEDOM RALLY Docketed:9 May 68.
    - Campus Peace and Freedom Party (org). SUPPORT THE OAKLAND SEVEN. Docketed: 2 May 61.
    - Campus Students for a Democratic Society (org). DIAL-A-SCAB TODAY. Pink stock. Docketed: 2 May 61.
    - Campus Students for a Democratic Society (org). SD PRESENTS / MANY FACES OF U.S. IMPERIALISM. Docketed: 22 Apr 68.
    - Campus Young Socialists (org). FRED HALSTEAD / SOCIALIST WORKERS PARTY PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE. Off-white stock. Docketed: 23 Ap 68.
    - CCNP (org).SONS AND DAUGHTERS written & Directed by Jerry Stoll. Pink stock, illustrated. A flyer for second big week is elsewhere in this archive. THE GRATEFUL DEAD perform. Peach stock, illustrated. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 11 Oct 67.
    - CCPA (org). PROTEST CENSORSHIP BY THE DAILY CAL.
    - CHIC EDWARDS ASUC SENATE VOTE PACT. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handoutTues 9 May 67.
    - Civil Action Day Committee (org). WITH ALL THE LIFE THAT IS IN US WE MUST MAKE AN END TO THIS WAR. Illustrated. Docketed: Ban-Tel handout 5 Oct 67.
    - Civil Action Day Committee (org). Call for CIVIL DISOBEDIENCE & SUPPORT VIGIL. Yellow stock, 4pp, with attachment. Docketed: Ban-Tel handout 21 Nov 67.
    - Committee of Concerned Students (ad hoc) (org). WHERE IS REASONTHINK. Yellow stock. Mon Dec 5, 1966.
    - COPS ON CAMPUS / STRIKE!... Docketed: Thurs Dec 1, 1966.
    - CORE (org) THE HISTORY OF CORES RESTAURANT PROJECT. East Bay Restauranteurs hiring policies. Yellow stock. SIP-IN MARCH.
    - Draftable Students Union (org) IS THE DRAFT IN YOUR FUTURE? Yellow stock. Docketed: 16 April 68.
    - Ecumenical Exchange (org). FORUM ON RESISTANCE. Sunday October 8. [Sproul] Plaza handout noon 5 Oct 67.
    - ELECT DOUG TAYLOR Rep at LargeSPARK. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 9 May 67.
    - ELECT JOHN PETERSON / Rep at Large SPARK. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 9 May 67.
    - ELECT MARK NELSON Rep at LargeSPARK. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 9 May 67.
    - Evans (Rowland) + Novak (Robert) THE AGONY OF BERKELEY. Column reprinted from The SF Examiner, October 1, 1965, with cover slip for enclosed newspaper column.
    - FOR THE SAFETY AND ORDER OF THE MARCH ON BOVEMBER 20th
    - Free Speech Movement (org). Free Speech Movement SONGS. Docketed: Fri Dec 2 66.
    - Friends Center (org). STEERING COMMITTEE MEETINGSymposium on Foreign Policy etc.
    - GIDO RALLY. Schorer, Wolin, Wofsey / an ACLU lawyer speak. Blue stock. Docketed: 9 May 68.
    - Heyns (Roger W.) = Chancellor, University of California, Berkeley. UNIVERSITY TRADITION AND SOCIAL CHANGE. Speech at The Commonwealth Club, November 12, 1965. 8 leaves.
    - Independent Socialist Club (org). Draper (Hal) THE MIND OF CHARLES HITCH / forum. Illustrated. Thursday Oct 12. Docketed Ban-Tel handout 10 Oct 67.
    - Independent Socialist Club (org). CULTURAL RADICALISM AND AMERICAN CAPITALISM: The Avante Garde in American Life. Forum by Charles Capper. Wed. May 10. Art design by Lyons. Green stock. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 10 May 67.
    - Independent Socialist Club (org). IN DEFENSE OF SELF-DEFENSE. Of Black Panther Party in part. Illustrated. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout10 May 67.
    - Independent Socialist Club (org). NO CONFIDENCE/ verso: Cartoon of policeman beating student with image of the campus campanile, by Lisa Lyons. Docketed Dec. 5, 1966 / Mon.
    - John George for Congress Committee (org). PLEDGE OF SUPPORT TO DRAFT RESISTERS. George a black candidate. Docketed: 9 May 68.
    - JOHN GEORGE FOR CONGRESS. Oakland, CA. Blue stock. Black candidate. Docketed: 11 April 68.
    - Kent State Legal Defense Fund, Inc. OVERKILL AT KENT. Orange, yellow & red printing/stock.. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 28 Nov 67.
    - McCARTHY CANVASS OPENS IN LOS ANGELES. Docketed: 22 Apr 68.
    - Movement for a New America (org). PRESENTS PAUL KRASSNER.
    - NAACP Contribution Fund (org). HE HAD A DREAM / MARTIN LUTHER KING, JR. / 1929-1968.
    - PACT (org on University of California, Berkeley campus). DICK BEAHRS / ASUC PRESIDENT. Campaign literature.. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza Tues May 9 67.
    - PARTY / HELP STOP THE DRAFT WEEK. Peach stock, small map. [Sproul] Plaza handout 6 Oct 67.
    - Peace and Freedom News (org). Reprint, newsprint from this serial. Supporting Michael Jones for County Supervisor, Peace and Freedom Party black candidate. Newsprint, folded. Docketed: Door-to door handout / W. Berkeley 28 April 68.
    - Pitschel Players (org). THE W.C. FIELDS MEMORIAL ORPHANAGE. Revue by the Pitschel Players. Orange stock. Ban-Tel handout 6 Oct 67.
    - POT SALE / At the Weavers. 3 color silk screen. Mailed to Charles Polk. Ceramics but the pun & date are timely (& intended?)
    - Progressive Labor Party (org). COLUMBIA STUDENTS STRIKE FOR ALL OF US! Yellow-orange paper. Docketed: 2 May 68.
    - Resistance (org) ACTION ON THE DAY OF THE 16th. Green stock.
    - Resistance (org). TONIGHT / FORUM / DRAFT REFUSAL. Light tan stock.. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout noon Tues 2 May 67.
    - RON MERENBACH FOR SENATOR 1968. Yellow stock.. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 27 Nov 67.
    - Rousseas (Stephen) ELECTIONS OR COUP? / THE DEADLOCK IN GREECE. 6pp. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout noon Wed 26 April 67.
    - San Francisco State College (org). COME TO A TEACH-IN ON THE OPPRESSION OF WOMEN. Men are welcome.
    - SCAL (org). BOYCOTT S & W. Black & red inks.
    - Schwartz (Charles), Physics professor, for faculty members of CDO (org). DEAR COLLEAGUE= open letter dated May 8, 1968. 2 leaves. Docketed: Hist Department mailboxes / 8 May 68.
    - SDS (org). S.D.S. GENERAL MEMBERSHIP MEETING Wednesday May 8. Docketed: 7 May 68.
    - SDS (org). SDS / DEMOCRACY OR THE DRAFT.
    - SDS Draftable Strudents Union (org). LIFE AND PROTEST IN THE ARMY. Yellow stock. Docketed: 2 May 68.
    - SELF-DETERMINATION FOR THE VIETNAMESE! March Nov 15 / SF. Illustrated.
    - SF Community Press (org). Illustrated poster / DEMONSTRATE JAN 20 / SIGN AND ABIDE BY VIETNAM PEACE AGREEMENT. Art by R.K.M., 1972.
    - Socialist Labor Party (org). AUTOMATION: A JOB KILLER! / Curst or Blessing? Off white stock. Docketed: 11 April 68.
    - Socialist Workers Campaign Committee, NYC (org). VOTE SOCIALIST WORKERS IN 68.
    - SOME PEOPLE DONT LIKE TO HEAR NEW POINTS OF VIEW. Illustrated.. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout noon Thurs 27 April 67.
    - Spartacist West 1:9 (Dec 9, 1966)
    - Spartacist West 2:2 (Oct 3, 1967)
    - Spartacist-West 15 (April 27, 1968)
    - Student West Oakland Project (org). WHAT CAN YOU DO NOW? / NOTHING, OR. Docketed: 11 April 68.
    - SUPPORT BOYCOTT OF DEANSGATE MENSWEAR. Orange stock. Joint sponsors: ASUC Senate; AFSCME 1695; AFT 1474 + AFT 1570. Orange stock. Docketed: 11 Apr 68.
    - SYMPOSIUM ON PROTEST / May 8,9,10. Docketed: 7 May 68.
    - THE FACULTY SPEAKS OUT BOLDLY. Noon rally today. / The Strike Committee. Docketed: Tues Dec 6, 1966.
    - Twentieth Century Mobilization (org). A CALL TO THE NATION. 2 leaves.
    - University of California, Berkeley. A STATEMENT BY CHANCELLOW HEYNS. Dec 5, 1966 / Mon.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Academic Senate. NOTICE OF MEETING for Monday, December 4, 1967. Blue paper. Dated November 27, 1967. 10pp.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Faculty Peace Committee (org). PROFESSOR FRANZ SCHURMANN JUST BACK FROM 19 DAYS IN HANOI.
    - University Young Democrats (org). SUPERVISOR JACK MORRISON. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 13 Oct 67 AM.
    - VETERANS FOR PEACE (org). So headed, blue paper.
    - Vietnam Day Committee (org) DEAR COLLEAGE= open letter dated October 12, 1965.
    - Voice (org). VOICE / GENERAL MEETING. Docketed: 2 May 68.
    - Voice (org). VOICE PLATFORM. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout noon 10 May 67.
    - West Coast Committee for Democracy (org). OXI / GREEK MILITARY JUNTA / Protest March. Tuesday April 23rd. Docketed: 23 April 68.
    - WHY KENNEDY? Three leaves, legal size. Docketed: 23 April 68.
    - WHY SPARK? Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 9 May 67.
    - Young Socialists for Halstead and Boutelle (org). THE REAL CHOICE IN 1968. Yellow stock. Docketed: 15 April 68.
    - Young Socialists for Halstead and Boutelle (org). THE REAL CHOICE IN 1968. Docketed: 11 April 68.
    - YPSL (org). THE GREAT TRANSFORMATION. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout10 May 67.
  - File 12 (Box 2, Folder 28-29)
    - Ad Hoc Committee of Concerned Women / Campus Committee for Bay Area Citizens Witness for Peace in Vietnam (orgs). MOTHERS MARCH FOR PEACE IN VIETNAM. Map. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 12 May 67.
    - ALL TROOPS HOME NOW / MARCH IN S.F. Nov. 15. Bumper sticker in pink and black.
    - Another Mother for Peace (org). ALL OUR SONS IN VIETNAM ARE POWs. BRING THEM HOME! Bumper sticker in orange and black.
    - Another Mother for Peace (org). ANOTHER TAXPAYER FOR PEACE. Bumper sticker in orange and black.
    - Bay Area Spartacist League (org) FREE SPEECH & THE MULFORD ACT. Pink stock. Tuesday, Oct. 22.
    - Berkeley Community for McCarthy (org). McCARTHY FOR PRESIDENT A CALL FOR SUPPORT. Docketed: Hist Dept Mailboxes / 28 May 68.
    - Berkeley Student Support Group for the Poor Peoples Campaign (org). SUPPORT THE POOR PEOPLES CAMPAIGN. Docketed 6 May 68.
    - Better Berkeley Council (org). WHERE ARE YOU? Illustrated. Docketed: 18 Sept 68.
    - Black Panther Party (& other orgs) PEACE AND FREEDOM MOVEMENT OF ALAMEDA COUNTY, AREA ONE / open letter to fellow registrants and supporters. 4 leaves. Paul Jacobs, Huey P. Newton, & Mike Jones involved.
    - Black Panther Party (et al), sponsoring or participating orgs. RALLY TO SUPPORT STRIKING FARMWORKERS. Bill Brent of the Panthers spoke. Docketed: 7 Aug 68.
    - Black Panther Party (org) + C.P.E. (org). VIGIL TODAY Following Noon Rally with Eldridge Cleaver. Docketed: 3 Oct 68
    - Black Panther Party (org) + Campus Peace and Freedom Party (org). SUPPORT THE SAN QUENTIN PRISONERS. Caged Panther image. Rally, Cleaver et all spoke. Docketed: 2 Aug 68.
    - Black Panther Party (org) + Center for Participant Education and Individuals Representing the Campus Community (org). CLEAVER COURSE POSITION PAPER. October 1968. 13pp.
    - Black Panther Party (org) + Peace and Freedom Movement (org). SHOW YOUR SUPPORT FOR HUEY!. Illustrated. Docketed: 28 Aug 68.
    - Black Panther Party (org). BLACK IS BEAUTIFUL (with panther image). Orange and black bumper sticker.
    - Black Panther Party (org). SET HUEY FREE! Printed in LA by Aldine Co. Bumper sticker in green and black.
    - Bond / The Servicemans Newspaper 2:6 (June 11, 1968). Newsprint, illustrated.
    - C.P.E. (= Center for Participant Democracy), (org). WATCH OUT FOR A COP OUT. Docketed: 3 Oct 68.
    - C.P.E. (org) A DISGUISED COP OUT. Docketed: 3 Oct 68.
    - California Library Association, Mrs. Rose M. Towns, Chairman (org). THE FREEDOM TO READ. Blue ink. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 16 May 67.
    - Callison (William) STOPPING THE DRAFT: LETS THINK IT THROUGH (stapled to) THE SOCIALIST ANTI-WAR UNION. Two sheets, 4 pp. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 22 May 67.
    - Campus Friends of FUB (FUB = Free University of Berkeley). WHAT HAVE YOU DONE ABOUT YOUR EDUCATION? Light pea-green stock. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 12 May 67 (accompanied The Minority of One).
    - Campus Friends of FUB (org). THE MINORITY OF ONE / Ms. Arnoni DISCUSSES US WAR POLICY. Illustrated. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 12 May 67 (accompanied What Have You Done About Your Education.
    - Campus Mobilization Committee (org). HELP PLAN EAST BAY SUPPORT FOR THE G.I.S MARCH AGAINST THE WARon Thurs. Sept 19.
    - Campus Mobilization Committee (org). MARINES INVADE THE DMZ / N. VIET NEXT? / 235 Killed Last Week. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 24 May 67.
    - Campus Mobilization Committee (org). MARINES INVADE THE DMZ / N. VIET NEXT? / 235 Killed Last Week. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 25 May 67.
    - Campus Movement for a New America (org). HELD OVER!.....SONS AND DAUGHTERS. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 24 May 67.
    - Campus Movement for a New America (org). HELD OVER!.....SONS AND DAUGHTERS. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 25 May 67.
    - Campus Peace and Freedom / Black Panther Party (orgs). THE NEWTON-SEALE CAMPAIGN COMMITTEE PRESENTS A FORUM ON BLACK LIBERATION / verso: CLEAVER & U.C. FACISM.
    - Campus SDS (org). BERKELEY CONFERENCE ON BLACK POWER AND ITS CHALLENGES / revised schedule of speakers.
    - Campus SDS (org). COME TO THE REGENTS MEETINGHFIGHT U.C. RACISMFriday April 18. Docketed: 11 Apr 69.
    - Campus SDS (org). HIRE BLACKS & BROWNS ONLY / WIPE OUT RACISM AT U.C.! Docketed: 31 July 66.
    - Campus SDS Anti-Draft Committee. STOP THE WAR! STOP THE DRAFT? Illustrated.
    - Campus Spartacist Club (org). CZECHOSLOVAKIA: The Meaning of the Dubcek Reform Program. Green ink on blue stock. Docketed: 7 Aug 68.
    - Campus Stop the Draft Week (org). NO DEADLINE / THE FIGHT GOES ON. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 20 Nov 67 with further extended pencil docket below.
    - Campus YSA. ERNEST MANDEL. Illustrated. Docketed: 4 Oct 68.
    - CCS (org) Bulletin: DISCIPLINARY PROCEDURES AND PRACTICES ON CAMPUS
    - Clark (Tom) = Bay Area poet. CHRISTMAS ON TELEGRAPHG. Broadside poem, signed by the poet. Reprinted by permission of Black Sparrow Press. Printed by Okeanos Press. Black and red printing on orange stock. Published by Moes Books on Telegraph Avenue for the New Year 1996.
    - Community for New Politics LETS GET OUT OF THE WARFARE STATE
    - Council of Campus Organizations (org). DECEMBER 8th or FIGHT
    - Defender (Oakland), (org). Free Speech TRIAL NEWSLETTER. April 18, 1965. 6pp plus address leaf.
    - Defender (Oakland), (org). Free Speech TRIAL NEWSLETTER. April 25, 1965. 5pp
    - Dick Gregory for President Committee (org). THIS LEAFLET IS FOR PEOPLE[= beginning]. Docketed: 1 Aug 68.
    - Faculty Peace Committee (org) PRESENTS JOHN GERASSI. Yellow stock.
    - Faculty Peace Committee (org). THE SOCIAL RESPONSIBILITY OF THE INTELLECTUAL Susan Sontag et al to speak. Yellow stock. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 18 May 67.
    - FACULTY TODAY FACULTY / NOON RALLYA DECLARATION OF CONSCIENCE CONCERNING THE WAR IN VIETNAM AND THE DRAFT. Four professors who will speak, among others, are named. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 25 May 67.
    - Forum International (org). AN AMERICAN RED GUARD (illustrated). Chris Milton will speak. Docketed 6 May 68.
    - Forum International (org). DEAR COLLEAGUE= open letter, July 26, 1968. Docketed: Hist Mailbox 1 Aug 68.
    - Forum International / Biafran Relief Group (org). BIADRAN RELIEF FUND. Docketed 7 Aug 68.
    - Free Speech Movement (org). Free Speech Movement A DECLARATION OF INDEPENDENCE. Orange stock dated 4/28/65
    - Free University of Berkeley (org). COUNTER CURRICULUM PROJECTorganizing meeting, Dec. 9, Friday (duplicate?)
    - Freedom for Adoptive Children (org) = sub-set of the Peace and Freedom Party (org). CALIFORNIA CAN BECOME THE FIRST STATE IN NORTH AMERICA TO BE FREE OF ADOPTABLE CHILDREN. Docketed 20 Aug 68.
    - IMPEACH REAGAN. Sticker, with stars border.
    - INDEPENDENT SLATE IM 1968. Docketed: 29 Aug 68.
    - Independent Socialist Club (org) CHANCELLOR REAGAN
    - International Registry of World Citizens (org). DECLARATIONwith WORLD CITIZENS PACT, 2 leaves
    - Kennedy Headquarters (org). CONGRESSMAN JOHN TUNNEY. Docketed: 6 May 1968.
    - McCarthy for President Campaign (org). YOU CAN HELP McCARTHY BE OUR NEXT PRESIDENT. 2 leaves. Docketed: Hist Dept. mailboxes 1 Aug 68.
    - National Conference for New Politics (org). DEAR FRIEND= open letter signed in type by Spock, Julian Bond and two others.
    - Office of Economic Opportunity (org) / distributed by AFT Local 1570 (org). AFT STRIKE / POVERTY FUNDS = LITTON PROFIT. [Sproul] Plaza handout 15 May 67.
    - Organization of Arab Students, Berkeley (org). ZIONISM, WESTERN IMPERIALISM, AND THE LIBERATION OF PALESTINE. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 16 May 67.
    - Peace and Freedom Movement (org). COME TO THE PEACE AND FREEDOM CONVENTION.. Docketed: 1 Aug 68.
    - Peace and Freedom Movement Area Groups 3, 4, 7 & 11 (orgs). PAUL JACOBS. Docketed: 6 May 68.
    - Peace and Freedom Party (org). SAVIO FOR STATE SENATE, bumper sticker in blue and orange.
    - Pearson (Drew) NEGRO CHILDREN STARVING NEEDLESSLY. Column reprinted. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 11 May 67.
    - PICKET THE OAKLAND INDUCTION CENTER. Docketed: Ban-Tel handout 12 May 67.
    - Port Chicago Vigil + Independent Socialist Club + Spartacus League + McCarthy for President Steering Committee (orgs). RUSSIA GET OUT OF CZECHOSLOVAKIA! / U.S. HANDS OFF!. Docketed: 21 Aug 68.
    - Professors for Scheer (org). DEAR COLLEAGUE=open letter, May 19, 1966
    - PUT X IN THE THIRD BOX / WHY WE WILL NOT VOTE FOR BROWN OR REAGAN.
    - Ramparts Magazine. A PRIMER ON VIETNAM. From the pages of Rampart Magazine, Newsprint.
    - Resistance & SDS Anti-Draft Union (orgs). NOON TODAY RALLY ON DRAFT RESISTANCE. Docketed: 11 May 68.
    - Resistance (org). CONFERENCE ON DRAFT REFUSAL. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 12 May 67.
    - Resistance [= group of men who are refusing any cooperation with the draft] (org). MAY 17th / SUPPORT DRAFT REFUSERS. [Sproul] Plaza handout 15 May 67.
    - Resistance. IS GUATEMALA THE NEXT VIETNAM? Docketed: ca 10 of 68.
    - Revolutionary Caucus (org) + Young Socialist Alliance (org) and other members of other organizations, participants. THE CHICANO STRUGGLE FOR SELF-DETERMINATION. Illustrated. Green stock. Docketed: 11 Apt 69.
    - San Francisco Vigil / Port Chicago Vigil (orgs). MOBILIZED? Sunday April 16 rally. Light tan stock.
    - Schlesinger (Arthur, Jr.) WHY I AM FOR KENNEDY. 5pp reprint from The New Republic, May 4, 1968, handed out. Docketed: 28 May 68.
    - SDS Black Power Day Committee. DEAR FRIEND= open letter dated October 11, 1966.
    - SDS, Labor Committee (org). MISCO IS ON STRIKE! Docketed: 9 Aug 68.
    - Sellers (Charles) FACULTY COLLEAGUES= open letter by professor on behalf of Eugene McCarthy for President.
    - SHAMEFUL CASE OF RACIAL DISCRIMINATION ON THE GOLDEN GATE BRIDGE. Docketed: Ban-Tel handout 24 May 67.
    - Slate (UC campus org). LIBERETY AND JUSTICE FOR ALL / verso: STATISTICAL MAGIC.
    - Slate = The New Slate (campus org). ITS TIME TO BELIEVE Docketed: 21 May 68.
    - SNCC Newsletter on pink stock, schedule of events, dance program on verso featuring THE GRATEFUL DEAD et al, illustrated.
    - Socialist Labor Party (org). REFORM OR REVOLUTION, WHICH IS THE BAD TRIP? Docketed: 21 May 68.
    - STATEMENT BY THE FACULTY OF THE DRAMATIC ART DEPARTMENT / University of California, Berkeley. Docketed: 3 Oct 68.
    - STEVENSON DEMOCRATS FOR KENNEDY. Bumper sticker in black and blue.
    - Student Mobilization Committee (org). GI TEACH-IN. Similar but not identical to another flyer with this title. Docketed: 6 Aug 68.
    - SUMMER VIETNAM. Small slip. Docketed: Ban-Tel handout 23 May 67.
    - TO THE FACULTY. Open letter from student leaders and six professors.
    - TONIGHT! FAMINE RELIEF PROGRAM FOR BIAFRA. Purple ink. Docketed: 1 Aug 68.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Academic Senate. Concerning: REPORT ON EFFECTS OF RESOLUTION No. 1. October 2, 1968.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Academic Senate. MEETING OF THE BERKELEY DIVISION. October 3 [1968], 4pp. Extensively annotated in blue ink by Leon Litwack indicating changes during course of meeting.
    - Universities National Anti-War Fund (UNAF) (org). A CALL TO THE UNIVERSITY COMMUNITY.
    - VIETNAM DAYS May 21 & May 22 / COMMUNITY MEETING. Schedule of Events.
    - Voice (org). VOICE (MAPS) WILL MEET TO ORGANIZE CAMPAIGN. Docketed: 6 May 68.
    - Wesley and Stiles Program Committee (org). THE CHILDREN OF VIETNAM. Buff stock. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 15 May 67.
    - Windmiller (Marshall) COMMENTARY (for Pacifica Radio) Number 29: VIETNAM AND THE BERKELEY CONGRESSMAN. April 7, 1966. 4pp.
    - Young Socialist Alliance (org). PAINTERS UNION PROTEST DEMONSTRATION Yellow stock. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 24 May 67.
    - YPSL, Norman Thomas Chapter (org). THE MIDDLE EAST WHAT DEMOCRATIC SOCIALISTS SAY: Yellow stock. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 25 May 67.
  - File 13 (Box 2, Folder 30-31)
    There is no item list for File 13.
  - File 14 (Box 2, Folder 32-34)
    - Abrams (Richard M.) THE STUDENT REBELLION AT BERKELEY. Offprint from The Massachusetts Review 6:2 (Winter-Spring, 1965)
    - AFT 1570 / Community Affairs Committee(org). INFORMATION LEAFLET / UNITED STATES INVOLVEMENT IN LATIN AMERICA / Number Two. Light tan stock. 4pp. Another, undated copy, is in the archive. Docketed: 14 May 68
    - ASUC (campus org). FREEDOM BALLOT TODAYVOTE.
    - ASUC (org). INDEPENDENTS / CHUCK EVERETT Orange stock, docketed.
    - Bay Area Inter-Universities Committee on Foreign Policy (org). Open letter to DEAR SIGNER OF THE LETTER TO PRESIDENT JOHNSON.
    - Bay Area Spartacist League. JAMES ROBERTSON WILL SPEAK Docketed. 1967. Yellow stock.
    - Black Panther Party (org). ITS ALL THE SAME. KNOW YOUR ENEMY on verso of cartoon of pigs. Other copy in archive does not have cartoon.
    - Black Panther Party (org). SOLEDAD BROTHERS DEFENSE CENTER (org). In envelope, unopened, posted 4 Aug 1971.
    - Boalt Hall (law) Students Association (org). INFORMATION ON CURRENT CAMPUS LEGAL PROBLEMS. 10pp, mimeo, purple ink.
    - C.N. C. (org in LA). Promoting COMMON SENSE sample copy, offering two other titles for sale.
    - Campus Draft Opposition (org). PLEDGE TO REFUSE INDUCTION. Docketed 15 May 68. Another copy (docketed May 9 68) is elsewhere in the archive.
    - Campus Draft Opposition (org). VIETNAM COMMENCEMENT. Friday May 17. Docketed 15 May 68
    - Campus Draft Opposition (org). VIETNAM COMMENCEMENT. Friday May 17. Docketed 14 May 68.
    - Campus Friends of Peace and Freedom (org). KNOW YOUR ENEMY! / NATIONAL POLICE WEEK. Docketed.
    - Campus Report II:13 (May 16, 1968)
    - Campus Young Socialist Alliance (org). SOCIALISM AND THE 1968 ELECTIONS. Illustrated. Docketed.
    - Catholic Students for Social Action (org) POSITION ON SPIDER and OBSENITY. Spider a political campus mag, CSSA disagrees with content, supports mags right to expression.
    - Cited Stuydents Union (org) ?NEGOTIATIONS? Docketed.
    - Cleveland (Brad) = UC graduate student. $20 MILLION increase in yearly budget of Berkeley 8pp.
    - CMC (campus Mobilization Committee). (org). MASS MEETING / STOP THE DRAFT WEEK Docketed.
    - CMC (org). MASS PICKET DEAN RUSK, Jan 11 1969. Docketed in Dec 1968.
    - CMC for M.A.P.S. (orgs). MAPS MEETING TONIGHT. Illustrated. Docketed.
    - Committee for a Creative Alternative (org). WHO CARES? Variant on blue stock. Docketed.
    - Committee for a Creative Alternative (org). WHO CARES? On green stock. Docketed: 16May 68.